(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
You're the owner here?
I'm the one who made this dish for you.
Good!
Would you be interested in doing a project with me?
If you want something, please come talk to me this way.
I'm going to do this project.
Next time, give me a banger.
Tao Sor, you should go rest.
Hey man, it's just a little cut
I think he's still got it.
What's your deal with Tao Sor?
You know.
We actually came here tobe taught cooking by you.
We were actually here last year, try your food, it was incredible, it was amazing.
You don't remember, do you?
I've heard people talk,
that the youngest son had disappeared for a while.
And once he came back,
he didn't really go anywhere.
Other people say,
he drowned.
Until his brain wasn't normal.
But, no one's ever confirmed what the real story is
and his family doesn't say much either.
Really?
What are you doing here all alone?
I'm just...
..here watching the sunset.
Then...
..let me sit here as well.
About today..
..I'm sorry.
I ruined your event.
What do you mean?
I don't know anything.
But... just forget it.
Us humans, there's gonna be some good times.
Some bad times.
They'll go by eventually.
I probably pressured you a bit too much.
It's okay
I'll just forget soon.
- Hey! You!
How are you doing?
You're okay, right?
Okay...
..okay about what?
You...
..don't remember what happened yesterday?
Yesterday...
Yesterday's incident?
Chef Mochi!
Better go hurry and draw!
Wait a minute, Daiji.
What...
..happened to me yesterday?
Well, yesterday..
Well yesterday, he came to eat at our restaurant
and said that your cooking is exquisite! Okay?
Um, Chef Mochi, you should go!
I'll look after the customer, okay?
- Okay.
- Go on, go on.
What's going on?
So what's going on with Tao Sor?
Why does he look confused?
It's like he doesn't remember what happened yesterday
I'm begging you..
..can you please stop getting involved with Chef Mochi?
And, why do I have to?
There's gotta be something.
Why do you always keep messing with him?
Okay!
In that case, if you won't tell,
I'm going to post on social media
..that the chef here serves their customers poorly.
- Wait a minute.
Everyone has to know that this place doesn't...
- Wait, please, wait..
Chef Mochi can only remember a day at a time and...
Okay! Hold up!
Wait a minute...
Okay!
Come on! Okay!
Chef Mochi..
..has a problem with his brain.
He can't remember yesterday,
..neither can he remember his past.
Today's events can only be remembered today.
Having memories for only a day?
Is that possible?
Kim!
What are you doing?
Do you think
there can be a person that
can only have memories for a day,
and forget everything when they wake up the next day?
If you wanna know, it's not that hard.
Does a person who loses both short term and long term memory,
but only has memories of deach present day exist?
It is a very rare condition, but there are real reports, with two main categories
1. Trauma to the nervous system
which occur after brain surgery when the brain lacks oxygen
or when there is damge to the hippocampus.
With examples such an English musician,
who can't tell the day or month, but remembers his wife
2. Psychological Trauma
which occurs for immense emotional distress
such as being triggered emotionally.
Some cases forget their whole identity
or important situations in life.
There have been cases where subjects can only recall new experiences for a short period
and forget. Like a complete reset.
Chef Mochi..
..has a problem with his brain.
He can't remember his past,
Today's events can only be remembered today.
But..
Couldn't they also be faking it?
Like they're hiding from some truth?
Who would know, Kim?
I think things like this should be proven.
How so?
That's the thing.
Speaking of, what should I do to be able to meet again?
Who?
Siw!
Help me out with something.
Help with what?
Help with what, Kim?
Let's go for a run.
Run?
Run.
Excuse me?
Could you teach me how to do that?
Sure!
Here,
ah..the first thing is..
You've never done this?
Never!
Here, the most important thing is you have to release the lock.
- Ahhh.
- See? Release first.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Then slowly reel in, okay? Yes.
- Ahh...
do you let the line...
- Oh no, no, no, this one.
- Ahh..
Yes, don't rush either...
Most importantly, is...
Let me join your run!
Just wondering, what's your name?
It's Tao Sor, and how about you?
Why don't you try and guess.
There's a million names out there,
how am I gonna guess?
My name is...
Jackson, as in Michael Jackson.
I'm Tao Sor, how about you?
My name is Pop, like Soda Pop.
I'm Bruce. As in...
Bruce... Lee!
Pleasure to meet you.
I'm..
Peter.
Like...
Peter... Parker.
- The itsy bitsy spider climbing up the spout -
You can't remember me?
Nice view, right?
This is the very first time
that I feel like I want to come here often.
It's also my first time.
So why do you like running here?
It's a time where I can think about the day
and also...
hope that... I could remember.
You don't like taking photos?
I like drawing more.
Then...
let me take one photo, as a memoir
that at least for today, we know each other.
Amazing! That's really great!
That's cause I had a good teacher!
Well... that's true.
- Amazing!
- Could you take a picture for me?
Of course!
- Video's better.
- Okay
1, 2, 3!
Anyways, you still haven't told me your name.
My name is Kim.
- And I'm...
- Tao Sor.
To be honest, I already know your name.
Let's see each other later.
Let me shoot this.
Okay.
Let’s start with the food first
pick it up, go on.
And this is the first dish from Phuket that we helped each other make.
That's right, I have to say, it might not look as good as us, hey!
It might not look as good the chef's,
but as for the taste, let's give it a try and figure out!
Put it in my mouth.
How is it?
Woah! Delicious!
- Really?
- Try it for yourself.
How is it? Good, isn't it?
Mmh! Delicious!
I'll say, the taste surpasses it's looks by miles.
And for the next place we'll be taking you guys,
don't forget to follow and see!
See you soon!
Wait, wait, let me get another moment for the closing.
Ahh, okay... cut!
- Thank you guys so much for today!
- Thank you!
Um, if you'll be teaching any more recipes, don't forget to call me, Kim!
- Okay, thanks for helping me out today!
- No problem!
Also, once the edit's finished
upload and use my hashtag as well.
- Can do!
- No problem, bro!
In that case, should we leave?
- Thank you, thank you..
- I'll walk you back.
Kim!
You..
Remember me?
Oh...
No.
But just then I saw them call your name.
But...
..have we ever met each other?
Why...
..do I draw your portrait.
You...
..drew my portrait?
He just brings people to cook.
You don't know him or anything.
Wishing you a safe journey today. Hope everything goes smoothly.
See you again.
Next time, if you come again, I’ll take you to cook Thai food.
I love Thai food
Thai Sour Curry.
Kang Som.
Delicious.
Yeah, yeah you’re Thai now.
Bye.
Have a nice day.
- Thank you so much, bro. I'll get your commission later.
- Sure!
Bring her again!
Kim's pretty good, Dad.
Don't let him overstep his postion.
Next time, why don't you just let him do it?
Sang!
I've sent off the client now,
if you need anything next time, let me know.
Then next time don't get involved
I can do my own job!
Just stay put till the year is done and just leave.
What a sleaze.
We could've said things nicely, Sang
I'm here to help, for goodness sake.
Oh? Why are you here so fast?
Didn't you say you had a shift today?
You told me to hurry up!
I thought you were stressed about something.
At first, I was stressed.
But after seeing your face, it's all gone.
Don't tell me you brought a surgical knife out?
Is this the time to be teasing?
So what's your problem?
Well, since we're here..
You read my mind.
- Alright, let's go.
- Alright.
Doctor...
These days, Tao Sor seems to remember things a lot more.
You're afraid Tao Sor's gonna remember the things you don't want him to, right?
Tao Sor remembering isn;t an easy thing, you know?
He has to be exposed to the same situation for a good length of time.
Or maybe, something could've triggered his brain.
So what could've triggered him?
Um, electric currents,
..intense physical trauma,
What about a person?
A person?
This, I'm not sure.
Either way, can you come see Tao Sor often for the time being?
In case something happens, and you could quickly tell me.
Can do.
But you gotta treat me to dinner tonight
I'll get a you huge order of lobster.
One this big.
- Okay, cheers!
- Cheers!
Tao Sor, my name's Dr. Kleun, your on hand doctor
I probably don't have to introduce myself, do I?
Everyone remembers me...
...but I can't remember anyone.
Are you a real doctor? I don't even know.
This picture...
is the first drawing you did.
And this one,
is of the place you like to go exercise at.
Even if you tell me, I still wouldn't remember.
Even if you can't remember things,
it doesn't mean that you can't live life.
Doctor?
Do I have a chance to remember everyone?
I still wake up and recall
how much my parents love me
what I did at the beach,
I want to have memories like everyone else.
Whether or not you remember anything,
I want to let you know,
that everyone in your family loves and cares for you very much
and they'll take care of you, no matter what happens.
Next time, if you need me to pick you up, you can just tell me.
Could I?
Of course! I'm your cousin, after all!
Yeah?
I've never felt that way.
You sure are blunt.
It's true! When you were here, I was still really young.
How could I remember anything.
And you never came back to visit again.
How could I feel that way?
My mom, she...
has some bad history with this place.
So my family never came back.
Then, no problem.
We can just get close now, don't you think?
You serving me curry too?
Just the broth is enough!
Let's see, if you want the fish so much
then go ahead!
So you could be smart like everyone else.
What? I'm already smart!
There! Eat some vegetables too!
I guess so...
Siw!
About Sang...
...when did she become so cold hearted?
That case? She's actually very sensitive, you know?
But when she's in front of Dad, she has put on a strong act.
In that case, you can take care of the bill.
Wait, wait, wait. Did you get me out here to treat you dinner?
You still enjoy Orange Curry, don't you?
I don't like it.
Sang makes us have Orange Curry for breakfast, lunch and dinner.
What else would you have me eat? All I have everyday is Orange Curry.
Well, aside from Sang, you also have me.
I raised you off of Orange Curry.
Wait for it, a whole year full of Orange Curry for sure.
Kim, we gotta go. Get the bill!
What's going on, I haven't eaten yet!
Hurry up and eat!
Waiter? Get us the bill!
Hello, Ms. Suli, thank you for the stars
you sent a whole star shower, that's so nice! Thank you!
Okay everyone, we're now gonna go into the horoscopes for Leos.
This week, fortune for love will be strong!
You might just meet the one.
But...
You have to put in a little effort, you can't just sit around being pretty.
You might meet someone who hurts you.
What can I do to see the person I like? We're in different places.
They're an influencer that does fortune telling,
and I'm an influencer doing lifestyle content in Phuket.
If you want to see her, you have to go to her
you’ll have to find a way to make her come to you.
And since she’s an influencer
using work as a reason would probably be the most effective.
Do you want me to help think of a solution?
No need, I think I figured it out.
As for Virgos,
your luck in romance might not be so good.
Kim! Where you going so early?
I thinking of getting something to eat.
Oh, Sang. We're about to enter low season
I was thinking if getting some influencers to promote our boat would be good?
I think it's a waste.
Another thing, if we're entering the monsoon season, there still wouldn't be any clients.
Siw!
I like your idea.
- Really?
- Yeah!
Are you going to use it to promote your own business?
And why do we have to promote others?
Just promote the family's boat.
So that means you're in?
Come up with a plan of action then
so I can present it to Dad.
Will do!
And don't accepting any work elsewhere.
Are you drawing me right now?
If it's not okay with you, I can get rid of it.
Just wait a minute.
It looks good.
Let me take it
I'll buy it off you
I won't sell.
What are you, an indie artist?
But if you want it, I could give it to you.
Sure. Then...
..sign it for me too,
in case you get famous one day and I could sell it.
Alright..
Wanna go surfing?
Nah, I don't know how.
If you can't, then you should try learning!
Come on, I'll show you how it's done.
I've never been in the ocean.
Are you afraid of the ocean?
Try it out, I'll bring you out there. Trust me.
Is that really a good idea?
Why?
I've never been in the ocean before.
In that case, there might be another way.
What way?
I'll show you.
I don't know if you've been here or not, but I think
this place will make you feel like the ocean isn't a scary place.
Ready?
Scared?
Gradually start breathing to the rhythm of my voice.
Let your heart be free.
Breath in,
breathe out.
Now let's go inside.
If it's too much, close your eyes.
Follow me, okay?
Another step, go foward a little.
And now, open your eyes.
You see? Inside, it's breathtaking.
In Bangkok, I barely had any time to go anywhere.
So I came to the aquarium in secret alot.
I don't know if I've been here before either.
I might have, but..
I probably don't remember.
Aren't you curious why?
Let me tell you a secret.
Actually, you and I have met before.
Alright, I've told you my secret.
Now, it's your turn.
My secret is...
I can't remember yesterday's events.
But I can remember some pieces.
Like cooking,
drawing, but...
You saying that we know each other,
I don't know if it's true.
Then...
what else do you remember?
Tell me about it.
Oh!
I really like Tao Sor snacks
and I also like drawing.
I think I'm afraid of the ocean.
But...
Now I'm not afraid anymore.
Because...
the bottom is kinda pretty, don't you think?
Nown!
I'm here.
The cards really that bad?
To be honest, yes.
Both in your job and in your love life.
Whatever you hope for, you won't receive.
Whatever you hope against, you won't receive.
So why did you have me promote your family's business?